ACTWU's Legal Department Records 5619/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Hobgood-DOL, 1980-1983 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Ray Marshall vs. John Hutchens, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- NCFIR v. Ray Marshall, 1978-1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Marshall v. Ramsey No. 80-1490, 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Education Committee George C. Hood Incident, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Miscellaneous Newsletters & Articles on Roanoke Rapids, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Educational Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Company Articles, Ads, Propaganda, Etc., 1976 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Anti Union Committee (Work Folder), 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Letters, 1979-1983 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Miscellaneous Articles, etc., 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Anti Union Committee, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Employees Education Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. News Clippings, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. ACTWU, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. ACTWU Educational Committee, 1977-1981 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. ACTWU Anti-Union Literature, 1976-1978 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Patterson v. NLRB No. 78-74-Civ-8, 1978-1980 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Patterson v. J.P. Stevens NLRB, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Patterson v. NLRB 78-74-Civ-8 (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Patterson v. NLRB 78-74-Civ-8 (2 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Patterson v. NLRB 78-74-Civ-8 (3 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Marshall v. J.P. Stevens Education Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Educational Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (Sledge, Lucy) Civil Action no.1201, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids General & Contract, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Melvin Barnett Discharge, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Cynthia Bissette Discharge, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Carolyn Carlisle Discharge, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Henrietta Fleming (Piece Rate), 1982 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Brenda Martin Discharge, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Karen McAdams Discharge, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Dorothy Newell (Piece Rate), 1982 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (Harold Mayer Productions, Inc.), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Film (Testimony), 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Lauringburg-Scotland Operation Jerico [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Lauringburg-Scotland Operation Jerico [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Memo: Refusal to Supply Info in Form Requested, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Allendale, S.C. Plant Closing, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. J. R. Ax, 1981-1983 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Anti-Union Committee's, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Tim Brown, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Operation Jerico Formal Papers Lawsuit Laruingburg-Scotland, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Lucy Sledge, 1975-1981 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Lucy Sledge Petition for a Writ of Certiorari, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Lucy Sledge Briefs, 1976-1980 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Lucy Sledge et al. Briefs, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Lucy Sledge et al. Briefs, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- House of Representatives Hearings Committee on Education and Labor, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Tuesday, August 9, 1977
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. NLRB Briefs, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. NLRB Briefs and Appendix, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (Appeal of First Order) Petition for Certiorari, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, N.C. Case no.11-RC-2095 [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, N.C. Case no.11-RC-2095 [folder 2 of 3], 1965 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, N.C. Case no.11-RC-2095 [folder 3 of 3], 1965 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Reed Johnston 2nd 10J Application, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Reed Johnston 10J South Carolina CA-4494 Injunction, 1964-1965 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Franklin, N.H. (NLRB Cases), 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-2435 et al. Second Round Cases [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1970 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-2435 et al. Second Round Cases [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-2435 et al. Second Round Cases [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1966 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Appeal of First Order (Second Circuit) [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Appeal of First Order (Second Circuit) [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Appeal of First Order 4th Circuit, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-2180 et al. First Round Cases, 1967-1969 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-2435 et al. Second Round Cases, 1967-1969 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. NLRB Briefs, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Appeal of Second Order Petition for Certiorari, 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Arbitration, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Holidays, 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Insurance Benefits, 1975-1978 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Management Rights, 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Payment of Wages (Pay Practices), 1975-1980 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Pension Benefits, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Profit Sharing and Retirement Benefits, 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Rates of Pay, 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Safety and Health, 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Seniority and Interim Seniority, 1977-1980 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Severance Payments, 1976-1978 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Shift Premium Pay, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Strikes and Lockouts, 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Substitute Supervisors, 1974-1976 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Term of Agreement/ Effective Date, 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Union Security, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Vacations and Vacation Pay, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Workloads, 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Workweek, Hours, and Overtime, 1975-1980 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. MTM Job Study Method for Rate-Setting, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Motion to Reopen Record Various JPS Locations, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Affirmative Action Program: Handicapped, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Affirmative Action Program: Veterans, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Leave of Absence, 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wages - Rates of Pay, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Call-In and Reporting Pay, 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Discipline and Discharge, 1976-1980 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. First Aid and Health Monitoring Services, 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Adjustment of Grievances, 1974-1980 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Funeral Pay, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Rules of Employee Conduct, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Unsorted Bargaining Material, 1976-1978 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Status of Negotiations, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Company Manual, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. ACTWU Agreement, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Assignment File, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations Phase II Workloads, 1977-1979 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 2nd Circuit Appeals RRII, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Current File on Changes Proposed by Stevens in S-G Meetings., 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations Phase II Wages, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Perfect Attendance Awards, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations Phase II- Insurance, 1975-1978 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Group Insurance Policy Provident Chattanooga, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Contract Proposals, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  March-July 1978
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations, 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  August 1978-March 1979
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  March-June 1979
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  June-August 1979
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  September-December 1979
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  December 1979 - February 1980
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  April-September 1980
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations Phase II Minutes of Bargaining Sessions, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Moran Mills Fayetteville, N.C., 1983-1985 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Employee Handbook Fayetteville, N.C., 1984 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Fayetteville, N.C. Unemployment Cases, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Moran Mills Ltd. Case #11-RC-5258, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-11523 Fayetteville, N.C., 1985 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Fayetteville (Allen Johnson) Unemployment Appeal, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Fayetteville, N.C. Case no.11-RC-5258, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Fayetteville Louine Walker & Geraldine McKeithan, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Fayetteville, N.C. Case no.11-RC-5150 (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Fayetteville, N.C. Case no.11-RC-5150 (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, N.C. Case no.11-CA-6780, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Carter Plant 11-CA-10651, 10722 Shirley Coleman, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Bartacker General, 1981-1984 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-11472 FOIA Request, 1984-1985 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Gladys Mobley Grievance, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Mobley Arbitration Exhibits [folder 1 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Mobley Arbitration Exhibits [folder 2 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Gloria Scott Grievance, 1977-1983 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Shirley Edwards Grievance, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. New Milford, Connecticut, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case No.11-CA-11664, 1985-1987 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wallace, N.C. (Decertification), 1985 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wallace, N.C., 1986 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wallace, N.C. Master Agreement (Contract), 1982-1985 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wallace, N.C. 1980 Lay-Off, 1981-1983 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wallace, N.C., 1986 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. AMG, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-RD-415, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-RD-405, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-RD-405 Notice to Show Cause, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Delta Mills Committee of 100 Wallace, N.C., 1987 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-RD-405 Round 2, 1986-1988 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-RD-405, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Pension Profit Sharing, 1986-1988 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Legal, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Legal, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Manufacturers Hanover, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. National Citizens Committee, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. National Women's Committee, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Norma Rae Publicity, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Legal, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Organizing, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Organizing, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Organizing, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Organizing [folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Organizing [folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Printed Matter, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Printed Matter, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Organizing, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Printed Matter, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Printed Matter, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Printed Matter, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Settlement Letters, etc., 1980 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Public Relations, 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Social Justice, 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Social Services, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Staff Meeting, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Staff & Status Reports, Leadership Meetings [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Staff & Status Reports, Leadership Meetings [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1977 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Staff & Status Reports, Leadership Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Sale of the Statesboro Plant to Stevcoknit, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Stockholders, 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Stockholders Meetings, 1977-1980 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Strategy, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Strikes Insurance Program & Strikes & Demonstrations, 1973-1979 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Surveys Made by Outside Firms, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Testimony, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Johnston, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-6038, 6207, 6895, 1974-1977 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Compliance, 1980-1985 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Duplicate Copies of Union & Company & General Counsel's Papers, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. B 2nd Circuit Transfer to 4th Circuit RR I, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Westinghouse Circuit Race Research, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Material from Prep. of RRI Brief 4th Circuit, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids RR II Case no.11-CA-7252 [folder 1 of 3], 1979-1981 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids RR II Case no.11-CA-7252 [folder 2 of 3], 1978 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids RR II Case no.11-CA-7252 [folder 3 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR III 11-CA-7568) Biggs, Robinson, Statements Fab Lay-Off [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR III 11-CA-7568) Biggs, Robinson, Statements Fab Lay-Off [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids NLRB v. Florida Steel Corp. Civil Contempt Case, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Duplicate Copies - RR III, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR III) Willie Robinson 11-CA-7568 Biggs, Fab Lay-Off, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR IV) Case #11-CA-7972 Papers Ogletree Statement, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR IV) Case #11-CA-7972 Research Ogletree Statement [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR IV) Case #11-CA-7972 Research Ogletree Statement [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Florida Steel Wage Withholding Contempt Case, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Duplicate Copies (RR IV), 1979 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR V) Spinners & Doffers Lateral Transfer 11-CA-8071, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR IV) Roanoke Rapids, N.C. 11-CA-8071, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR VI) 11-CA-8226 Funeral Pay Changes [folder 1 of 3], 1979 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR VI) 11-CA-8226 Funeral Pay Changes [folder 2 of 3], 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RR VI) 11-CA-8226 Funeral Pay Changes [folder 3 of 3], 1979 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 11-CA-8504 Wage Increase, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Grady Cullom & Pansy Hasty, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Cafeterias 11-CA-8704 [folder 1 of 3], 1979 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Cafeterias 11-CA-8704 [folder 2 of 3], 1979 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Cafeterias 11-CA-8704 [folder 3 of 3], 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR X Cafeterias Papers, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR X Cafeterias 11-CA-8704, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Media Information Kit, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Walterboro, S.C. Affidavits & Statements 11-CA-9291 11-CA-9408 [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Walterboro, S.C. Affidavits & Statements 11-CA-9291 11-CA-9408 [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Walterboro, S.C. 11-CA-7283, 1978-1981 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Policy Manual Changes in Non-Union Plants, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Original Policy Manual, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wage Increase Papers 11-CA-8504, 8778 [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wage Increase Papers 11-CA-8504, 8778 [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 11-CA-8504,8778 Wage Increase Leaflets, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 11-Ca-8504,8778 Wage Increase Research Materials, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Allendale & Tifton Speeches Wage Withholding RR XI, 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Staff Meetings and Update Memos, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids 11-CA-8848 [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids 11-CA-8848 [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR XII Health Procedures: Proposals, Form 19s, Affidavits, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 11-CA-8848 RR XII Health Procedures - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR XIII Pension Plant Improvement- Trust Agreement, Actuarial Report, Ee Plan Booklets [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR XIII Pension Plant Improvement- Trust Agreement, Actuarial Report, Ee Plan Booklets [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Cotton Dust Citation, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 11-CA-8967 RR XIII Pension Plan Charge Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR XIV Wage Withholding, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, N.C. Bobby Lee Goods, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids 11-CA-9245 Alice Carter, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Negotiations Phase II Correspondence, etc., 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Project, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wage and Price Guidelines, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR XIII Pension Plan Charge. Extra Papers, 1976-1980 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Policy Manual Changes [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Policy Manual Changes [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. LBO, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. LBO-ESOP, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Constitutional Amendments Submitted by Affiliates, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Union Constitution, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 2nd Circuit Motion to Dismiss or Transfer: Research Material [folder 1 of 3], 1973-1979 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 2nd Circuit Motion to Dismiss or Transfer: Research Material [folder 2 of 3], 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 2nd Circuit Motion to Dismiss or Transfer: Research Material [folder 3 of 3], 1973 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (RRI), 1979 (Box 52, Folder 8)